{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733906012","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733906012"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733907060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733907060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733912192","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733912192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733913268","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733913264"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733916804","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733916804"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733917843","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733917843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733922196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733922195"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733923248","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733923248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733931650","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733931650"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733932722","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733932722"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733936635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733936634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733937699","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733937699"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733940874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733940874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733941906","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733941906"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733945525","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733945525"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733946576","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733946576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733958805","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733958804"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733959885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733959885"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733963601","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733963601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733964640","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733964640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733967535","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733967535"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733968592","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733968592"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733972072","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733972072"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733973120","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733973120"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733978271","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733978271"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733979312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733979312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733983810","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733983810"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733984853","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733984853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733987756","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733987756"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733988807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733988807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733992500","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733992500"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733993547","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733993547"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543733999397","data":{"timestamp":" 1543733999397"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734000455","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734000455"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734003367","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734003367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734004426","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734004426"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734009093","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734009092"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734010146","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734010146"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734016893","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734016893"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734017956","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734017956"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734021942","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734021942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734022986","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734022986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734025607","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734025607"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734026649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734026648"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734033269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734033268"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734034321","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734034321"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734037791","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734037790"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734038081","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734038080"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 54431132-d063-40f2-ad4a-69d24d2e9231"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734062074","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734062074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-4-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734068750","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734068750"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-5-1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734076373","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734076373"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-9-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734083591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734083591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734089486","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734089486"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734095546","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734095546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734102406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734102406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734102977","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734102976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" bc96c72e-f30b-4011-adff-56584340b322"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.x2s.Ax.rise.20"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_5-6-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734112001","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734112001"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734124351","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734124351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734128900","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734128900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734139685","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734139684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734141906","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734141906"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734144123","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734144123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734147061","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734147061"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734149290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734149290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734151495","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734151495"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734154742","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734154742"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734156826","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734156826"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734158910","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734158910"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734161856","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734161856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734164086","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734164085"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734166299","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734166298"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734169325","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734169325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734171664","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734171664"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734174015","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734174014"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734177059","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734177058"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734179175","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734179174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734181289","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734181289"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734184389","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734184389"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734186631","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734186630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734188848","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734188848"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734192179","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734192179"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734194579","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734194579"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734196982","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734196982"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734200120","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734200120"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734211584","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734211584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734213882","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734213882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734227343","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734227342"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734234121","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734234121"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734236322","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734236322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734239290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734239289"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734251049","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734251049"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734253443","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734253443"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734256554","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734256554"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734258921","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734258920"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734263580","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734263580"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734275901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734275901"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734278169","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734278169"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734280447","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734280447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734283708","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734283708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734285992","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734285992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734288256","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734288256"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734291723","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734291723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734294166","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734294166"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734296593","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734296592"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734299445","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734299445"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734301629","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734301628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734303829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734303828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734307312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734307312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734309669","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734309669"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734314351","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734314351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734329051","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734329051"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734335138","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734335138"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734337460","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734337460"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734340475","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734340475"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734342603","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734342603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734344749","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734344749"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734347973","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734347973"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734350211","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734350210"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734352455","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734352455"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734355635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734355635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734368295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734368295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734381948","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734381948"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734385270","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734385269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734387604","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734387604"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734389904","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734389904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734393052","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734393052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734395380","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734395380"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734397728","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734397728"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734401126","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734401126"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734401300","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734401300"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_095800"," gameId":" 3fa42917-1036-4a81-b7ba-72c21aa5adc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}